I have started a new Facebook group
called solution raising during social
distancing solution raising is what
we've been doing over together tech for
the last couple of weeks we've done
three so far
one on education one on food and when
I'm combating infectious disease we do
for a solution raising as we spend an
hour coming up with actual potential
solutions we could create right now
together so we spend 15 minutes talking
about what is currently happening in
that space that is good that it's bad
what is happening this is where most of
us concentrate our time so we're only
spending 15 minutes here it's clearly
not something you can cover fully in 15
minutes then we spend 15 minutes
envisioning a world that is amazing for
us as an individual they don't need to
match I don't need to we don't need to
pick one utopian world to live in to
what is your best version of Education
look like what does your best version of
food security look like then we spent
half an hour talking about a solution we
could create right now if we had 10,000
people and $100,000 one that is this is
a actual solution to the problem for
those 10,000 people and doable with
$100,000 and we've generated many
solutions in those three hours of
dedicated so far so I've started a
Facebook group so that everybody who
wants to can participate in solution
raisings on my schedule I'll be doing
two or three a week I will be the host
but the idea for the Facebook group is
anyone can host a discussion let's start
raising solutions let's emerge from our
social distancing isolation into a world
that has hope and potential let's use
this as a cocoon and emerge as beautiful
butterflies into the world so everyone's
invited I will on Twitter I will link
this in a comment below in the Facebook
group in a comment below and on YouTube
this will be linked in the description
so please come help us raise many
solutions we are going to have so much
fun during this time